All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict, which results in Horty detaining Zorro, Usopp, and Brook.
Get out of my way, Team Bay. I won't let you keep me here anymore.
Let me handle it. You stay put.
Shut up! Sanji said all that cool stuff and you still want to fight?!
If that is what it takes to make you listen to me, yes!
What did you say?!
Are you ready?
Well, I was going to break my heart into lament…
Can't Felix dig that out, Harley, David, jump up and you're wrong.
Mā had got a good look for us but…
Don't you.
Don't you spill me?
We also just popped up…
are still alive.
What a shot.
The battle is on at Conchcord Plaza.
Captain Horty sure is something else.
One second he's writhing in agony he from an overdose,
then he levels the whole town with a flick of his wrist.
No. Neptune's army is done for. Every last one.
They didn't stand a chance. Horty's too strong.
We're all done for.
Minister of the Right! Minister of the Left!
King Neptune!
Do something!
We've wasted enough time onto the plaza.
No! They're taking him away!
We couldn't do anything.
We were so close.
You're going to be okay.
After so long.
Please stay with us.
We were finally supposed to see results.
This was going to be our year at the World Summit.
Queen Otohime.
But then they had to come and ruin everything.
Someone help us!
Save the king!
If we don't stop them soon, he will be executed.
Surely, someone can fight.
What kind of fight?
Look, Ma!
This is the end of our whole country, isn't it?
This is the end of our country, isn't it?
This is the end of our country.
It's the end of our country who can't help you!
Come on, Captain. Quit blubbering.
Yeah, things will start looking up soon. Just get back in the game.
Like I would ever take advice from a couple of losers like you.
You guys have no idea what it's like having your heart broken.
These feelings are real. I've wanted her since I first saw her.
Sure, she was just a kid, but I knew if I married her, I could fulfill my ancestor's dream.
But what happened instead?
You're just not my type!
Not my type, she said.
When the words came to my ears, I felt my love grow.
A flawless haiku by Vandertek in the night, I suspect.
My soul.
It's aching!
After she rejected me, I felt like it was time for a change, so I cut my hair!
I just attacked!
I thought I'd kill her instead, but I can't even get that right!
I know she's alive because I can still throw things at her!
This is not Straw Hat's fault!
Blah!
Ha ha ha!
Wait. That's it!
What's so funny?
My idea!
If I can't end her existence, then I'll just have to end everyone else's!
It's gonna be great!
You'll see!
Ha ha ha ha!
Hmm?
Release our king right now, Horty!
Last warning!
I mean it! We will fire!
Run, soldiers! Don't throw your lives away!
It's not that easy here!
Seabear!
No!
Take this, you bastard!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! About time you got here! I was getting sick of waiting!
We finally made it, Yozo!
Be careful! He will cut you!
I have arrived! At last!
And now there is nowhere left for you to rot again.
We can't get in! They locked the entrance to the plaza behind them!
King Neptune!
Let's scale the wall! Maybe we can see inside!
This way! This way! This way! Hurry!
Yes! Hurry!
It's 5pm solid r possibilities!
No!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Seoul, look!
Hmm...
You can see!
Uh...
Oh, my God!
It's settled.
That boy sure gave me a lot of trouble, though.
We've wasted far too much time.
We need to be on our way now, Princess.
Okay.
We're leaving Hachi in your care, Kami.
Uh, right.
Let us make haste, Megalo.
Ah!
Let us make haste.
I thought you soldiers were supposed to protect this country.
My men.
Damn you, Hordy.
Look alive, boys.
That soldier's up to something.
You think so?
Looks like he's packing dynamite.
He's going to blow everyone up with some kind of suicide attack.
But if he does that, I'm going to turn into roasted squid.
The three princes should get here soon.
But I can take out at least one of you before they do.
Water shot.
Oh, crap.
How far can it go?
You hear that?
That whistling sound.
What is it?
And what is it?
Hey, am I crazy?
I was under the impression the water shot wasn't that strong.
I know it took a lot of energy steroid to get that tough, but still, that was incredible!
We never anticipated it changing your hair color or increasing your muscle mass so greatly, though.
How are you feeling, Captain?
Couldn't be better.
What happened here?
Why didn't the soldiers wait for us to have them?
Fukuboshi, Ryoboshi, Manboshi!
Don't underestimate them.
Both their ranks and their sea monsters have been empowered by a drug.
Now it makes sense.
On an even playing field, Neptune's army would never lose a sortie-do!
It's time to mumble!
Ready?
Why don't you understand?
You're all so pathetic!
You new fishman pirates are just a bunch of cowards!
The other islanders let go of their hurt feelings brought on by the humans' discrimination.
And despite the fact that humans murdered their hero and their queen, they're willing to forgive them.
Even after all of their suffering, they still sign their names, because they want to change the future!
Your Highness.
Prince Fukuboshi.
What you do undermines their efforts!
Can't you recognize their bravery?
You're kidding me, right?
Don't mistake their kindness for courage.
It gives the humans another excuse to take advantage of us.
We're of the ages!
Seven princesses!
Dragon Tower Gate!
The princess beat the sea monsters!
There's hope after all!
You seek revenge not for justice, but because of your own personal hatred.
I won't let you take the king's life, nor the island his citizens call home!
You will never have the Ryugu Kingdom!
We're safe!
We should have known we could count on the princes!
So you beat some sea monsters.
Do you think that means you've claimed victory?
We will never be defeated, because we've been granted a power that is absolute.
And with that power, we will rule this country the way it was always meant to be.
The future of this country is peace!
Peace with the humans, and peace with the monsters like you!
If we don't triumph here, we'll have failed, and it will be hundreds of years before we have another
shot at friendship with the human world!
Oh, is that a fact?
Well, then the winners of this fight will rule this country.
It's a good happening!
Hmm.
Oh...
Whoa!
Hey!
They look... stronger!
What? But how?
Too slow.
Huh?
Ah!
Roar!
Time is running short, Megalo.
Ja!
Be safe, Father.
We'll be there soon.
He's going to be fine.
I promise you, Princess.
This drug of yours is fearsome indeed, Horty.
Ja-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ja-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Shirohoshi and Jinbei hurry to Concord Plaza to free King Neptune.
But their rescue plan is cut short by a trap.
With the royal family now captured, Horty reveals a shocking truth about the history of his revolution.
While the island is seized with despair, Van Der Decken does something rash.
On the next, One Piece, a surprising confession.
The truth behind the assassination of Otohime.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!